

CONTACT

Phone

+8801723494591



Email

theahmedsabbir@gmail.com



Website

theahmedsabbir.github.io

SPECIALIZATIONS

HTML & CSS

Bootstrap

Javascript

JQuery

React JS

Vue JS

PHP

MySql

Laravel

React Native

Wordpress

LANGUAGES

English | Bengali | Hindi

SABBIR AHMFD

SOFTWARE ENGINEER | FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Experienced Full Stack Web Developer With Quality Skillset In Both Frontend & Backend Development. I have successfully completed 60+ projects like websites, web applications for clients of different countries. A passionate team player & problem solver with 4+ years of experience.

EXPERIENCE

LEAD SOFTWARE ENGINEER (LARAVEL)

EMICON TECHNOLOGY (DUBAI) | JAN 2021 - PRESENT

- Full stack application development based on requirements using Laravel, Rest api, ajax, vue/react js.
- Design database and create restful api for mobile applications.
- Lead junior developers and maintain ongoing projects

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (LARAVEL)

PRIMEX SYSTEMS, DHAKA | MAY 2020 - DEC 2020

- Build Web Application from Scratch using Laravel.
- Develop backend functionalities based on client requirement.
- Developing and implementing different third-party APIs

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

TECHNOCONSULT INTL LTD, DHAKA | AUG 2019 - MAY 2020

- Design and develop web application as per requirement
- Research and develop new features, explore new web technologies

WEB DEVELOPER

UCIL BANGLADESH | 2018 - 2019

- Communicate and provide technical support to local and international clients
- Maintain a version controlling system and project management tool
- Designing, developing, and testing UI for mobile and web applications

EDUCATION & TRAINING

ADVANCED WORDPRESS DEVELOPMENT

SOFTTECH-IT | 6 MONTHS TRAINEE

PHP & LARAVEL ADVANCED COURSE

SHIKHBE SHOBAI | 6 MONTHS TRAINEE

B.SC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING

UTTARA UNIVERSITY | CGPA 3.7

HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE

RAJUK UTTARA MODEL COLLEGE | SCIENCE | A+

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE

UTTARA HIGH SCHOOL | SCIENCE | A+(GOLDEN)